<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sahar Jiwani</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sahar Jiwani</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Data Project</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Both of my datasets involved New York City. My first dataset is about AirBNB data for New York City. This dataset, after I removed some extraneous variables, includes price, minimum nights, availability out of the year, and number of reviews, amongst other things. The second dataset involved New York City real estate data. This set includes tax class at time of sale, sale price, square footage, and zipcode, amongst others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Modeling</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Sahar Jiwani, sj26895
The researchers of this dataset were testing the IQ levels of post-comatose patients. The first variable, id, is patient’s ID number. The second variable, days, is the number of days after awaking from the coma that IQ was measured. The third variable, duration, is how many days the coma lasted. The fourth variable, sex, identifies if the patient is male or female. The fifth variable, age, is age at the time of injury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Enjoy Python</title>
      <link>/blog/my-blogpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/my-blogpost/</guid>
      <description>Python is an intuitive and easy to learn coding language for someone who comes from a beginner coding background. As someone with very little experience coding, I really enjoyed learning Python. I found is made more sense to me than other languages like R. Here are some examples of the ways python is a functional and easy language to use!
If faced with a long list, python makes it very easy to select certain entries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have been working on:
-Project 1 -Project 2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>#SHADOWING AND WORK EXPERIENCE
Kunik Orthodontics
June 2018-August 2018 • Shadowed the orthodontist and hygienists on different cases • Learned the intricacies behind several unique, active cases
Texas House of Representatives- Legislative Intern January 2018-May 2018 • Corresponded with constituents and connected them to beneficial government resources • Handled specific constituent casework and helped resolve issues they faced • Scheduled events and maintained the district calendar for the Representative</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>